you did it on purpose I can see it in your eye لقد فعلت ذلك عن قصد، أستطيع أن أرى ذلك في عينيك،
لقد فعلت ذلك عن قصد، أستطيع أن أرى ذلك في عينيك،
bona fide no disguise no more goodbyes صدق، لا تمويه، لا مزيد من الوداع
صدق، لا تمويه، لا مزيد من الوداع
slurring your words like you didn't care تتلعثم كلماتك وكأنك لا تهتم،
تتلعثم كلماتك وكأنك لا تهتم،
notorious believing hearts in despair مشهور بسوء السمعة بترك القلوب في حالة من اليأس
مشهور بسوء السمعة بترك القلوب في حالة من اليأس
your index finger points blame at me
تلقي نقاط السبابة باللوم علي
but it pacifies nothing can set me free
لكن لا شيء يمكن أن يحررني
and all fairness I tried my best
وبكل انصاف بذلت قصارى جهدي
But delving too deep, it’s a heavy chest.
لكن الخوض في العمق، إنه صندوق ثقيل.
Lunatic, you called me so sarcastically,
أيها المجنون، لقد اتصلت بي بسخرية
Belligerent words that burned so fiercely.
كلمات عدوانية احترقت بشدة
Snagged in the web of your unsightly lies,
تعثرت في شبكة أكاذيبك القبيحة
I couldn’t escape, no matter how hard I tried.
لم أستطع الهروب مهما حاولت
My intestine twists, feels the threat,
أمعائي تلتف، تشعر بالتهديد،
Surplus pain is all I’ve accumulated yet.
الألم الفائض هو كل ما جمعته حتى الآن.
Your love was a weapon, used like a sword,
حبك كان سلاحا، يستخدم مثل السيف،
And I fiercely fought, but couldn’t afford it.
وقاتلت بشدة، لكنني لم أستطع تحمل تكاليفها.
You were a storm, I was just the rain,
كنت عاصفة، كنت مجرد المطر،
Falling so hard, swallowed by the pain.
يسقط بشدة، يبتلعه الألم.
In all fairness, I thought we’d survive,
بكل إنصاف، ظننت أننا سننجو
But delving too deep, I’m barely alive.
لكن الخوض في العمق، أنا بالكاد على قيد الحياة.
Lunatic, you called me so sarcastically,
أيها المجنون، لقد اتصلت بي بسخرية
Belligerent words that burned so fiercely.
كلمات محاربة احترقت بشدة.
Snagged in the web of your unsightly lies,
تعثرت في شبكة أكاذيبك القبيحة
I couldn’t escape, no matter how hard I tried.
لم أستطع الهروب مهما حاولت
Now I’m left with the pieces, broken and torn,
الآن بقيت لدي القطع، مكسورة وممزقة،
Threats in your voice, so sharp and worn.
تهديدات في صوتك، حادة للغاية  و بالية.
Fiercely you held me, but let me fall,
لقد حملتني بشدة، لكن تركتني أسقط
Surplus heartache, I’ve lost it all.
وجع القلب الفائض، لقد فقدت كل شيء
You did it on purpose, you knew what you’d do,
لقد فعلتها عن قصد، وعرفت ما ستفعله،
Accumulated sorrow, I can’t get through.
الحزن المتراكم، لا يمكنني تخطيه.
In all fairness, I’m letting you go,
بكل إنصاف، سأتركك تذهب
But deep down, you’ll never know.
لكن في أعماقك، لن تعرف أبدًا.